Contact

shelleyhathorn@yahoo.com

www.linkedin.com/in/shelleyhathorn-bsn-rn-65005218 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Healthcare Management BLS Clinical Research

Shelley Hathorn BSN,RN

ER travel nurse

Houston, Texas Area

Summary

Experienced Travel Registered Nurse with a demonstrated history of working in the staffing and recruiting industry. Skilled in Clinical Research, Patient Advocacy, Medical-Surgical, Pediatrics, and Patient Education. Strong healthcare services professional with a Bachelors of Science focused in critical care Nursing from Chamberlain College.

Experience

Houston, Texas Area

HealthTrust Workforce Solutions (formerly Parallon Workforce Solutions)
Emergency Room Travel RN
February 2009 - Present (11 years 5 months)

CHRISTUS St. Catherine Hospital

August 2005 - January 2009 (3 years 6 months)

Education

Chamberlain College of Nursing

Bachelors of Science, Registered Nursing/Registered Nurse (2015 - 2017)

Lamar University associates degree RN 2008, Registered Nursing/Registered Nurse · (2005 - 2008)